

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

# **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and Wordpress template might eventually be home to a fit of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

# **EDUCATION**



### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. hose to garble a well-known (but non-Biblical-that would have b administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

# **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

# **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

# Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult to the same level as any other visual element. The text simply becomes another supporting and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

# **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

# **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

# Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and
- Assist to il molestiae consequatur, vel ill goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

# **ACTIVITIES**



Sep 2003 - 2007

#### **CVPRO JSC**

### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer wn a 1914 Latin edition of De Finibus which challenges McClintock's 15th century claims and sugg' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

# **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

# HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni

- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US êm các từ ngữ hóm hỉnh hay thiếu trật tư. 5 đoạn từ kí tự danh sách

# **REFERENCES**



# **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

# SKILLS





# **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt iqua. Ut enim ad mi and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities